alsearsmd.com 2012-06-25

# Privacy Policy | Health Newsletter

  * Dr. Sears recognizes the importance of protecting your personal information and your trust in us. Therefore, we take the responsibility of handling your personal information extremely seriously.

## Your E-mail Address

When you subscribe to any of our e-mail newsletters, your address is added to our database. We’ll use your address to send your issues and to notify you of opportunities or products we think you might be interested in.

We will not sell, rent, or in any other way share your e-mail address with anyone.

You can remove your address from our mailing list by following the instructions at the end of every e-mail we send.

IIf you receive unsolicited commercial e-mail (spam) that you believe came from us, please send us an e-mail using our [online contact form](http://www.alsearsmd.com/contact-us/#form "Online contact form").

## Personal Information

Our staff will never ask you for personal information, such as your credit card number, except when you’re placing an order. At that time, we’ll require only the information needed to complete and fulfill your order.

We won’t _ever_ ask for information that’s not needed to complete your order—for example, we would never need to know your social security number. If anyone claiming to represent us asks you for this kind of information, you should refuse to give it and contact us at once.

Only our authorized employees will have access to this information. We won’t sell, rent, or share it in any way, unless required to by a law enforcement agency.

Please note that “personal information” doesn’t necessarily include your mailing address. See _Your Mailing Address_ , below.

## Confidentiality

Any correspondence you send to us, including e-mail, is considered confidential unless you tell us otherwise. We will not add your name to our e-mail list without your permission. We won’t quote you in our issues, on the web sites, or in promotional materials without your consent.

If you contact us to inquire about an order, our customer service staff will ask you to verify your identity by confirming information already in your record.

## Your Mailing Address

When you give us your mailing address, we will use this information to fulfill your order and to send you information on other products you might find interesting. If you don’t want us to send you this other information, please contact our customer service department:

Customer Service  
11903 Southern Blvd. Ste. 208  
Royal Palm Beach, FL 33411

Or you can email us using our [online contact form](http://www.alsearsmd.com/contact-us/#form "Online contact form") or call us toll-free at 1.866.792.1035.

## Cookies

Cookies are tiny files placed on your computer by web sites you visit. They can be used to make your next visit to that site more convenient (by remembering settings, for example).

Our web sites use cookies only to track how many people visit each page, how long they stay, and that sort of statistical data. We don’t store or collect any personal information with cookies.

Be Sociable, Share!

    *
